{
    "id": "650101a8b5374e83b7eef1514cf7bdb7",
    "title": "Subject verb agreement worksheet",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "bebe2770c3ed401eb2babaf4e526edfc",
            "title": "Subject Verb Agreement Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "One of my friends ..................... .. gone to France.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Each of the boys ..................... . given a present.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was",
                        "were"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Neither of the contestants ..................... .. able to win a decisive victory.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was",
                        "were"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Oil and water ..................... .. not mix.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "does",
                        "do"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He and I ..................... .. at Oxford together.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was",
                        "were"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Slow and steady ....................... the race.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "win",
                        "wins"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Neither Peter nor James ....................... any right to the property.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "No prize or medal ………………….. given to the boy, though he stood first in the examination.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was",
                        "were"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Either Mary or Alice ..................... responsible for this.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "are"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Neither the Minister nor his colleagues .....................…… given any explanation for this.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}